NLRB Briefs, Petitions and other Legal Documents 5318
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New Madrid, Co., and Jones Manufacturing Company., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Newberry Lumber & Chemical Company, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company, a Corporation, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Independent Employees Association of New Idea, Inc., 1940 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Neuhoff Packing Company and Swift & Company, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- New York Telephone Company, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Parkside Hotel, and Parkside Hotel, Inc., a Corporation, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Washington, Virginia, and Maryland Coach Company, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Waterman Steamship Corporation, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Weil-K (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Weil-Kalter Manufacturing Company, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Weirton Steel Company, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Wells, Inc., 1947 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Wentworth Sales Company, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- West Coast Casket Company, Inc., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- West Kentucky Coal Company, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- West Ohio Gas Company, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- West Texas Utilities Company, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Wheatland Electric Cooperative, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- West Virginia Glass Specialty Company, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Westex Boot and Shoe Company, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Westinghouse Electric Supply Company, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Westinghouse Electric Corporation, Ansonia Plant, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Rehrig-Pacific Company (Box 10, Folder 52)
  No date. NO. 13660
- Ideal Leather Novelty Company, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Steinberg & Company, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- The Kramer Company (Box 10, Folder 55)
  No date. NO. 4835
- Louise Hamilton, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Lloyd A. Fry Roofing Company, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Modern Cleaners Company, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- La Crosse Telephone Corporation, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Mac Smith Garment Company, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Max Sax, d/b/a Container Manufacturing Co., 1948 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Victor Manufacturing & Gasket Company, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Vermont American Furniture Company, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Venetian Blind Workers Union, Local 2565, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Vane A. Cameron and Raymond G. Franks, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- United Mine Workers of America, District 2, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- United Mine Workers of America, District 31 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- United Hoisting Co., Inc., and Local No. 15C, Intl. Union of Operating Engineers, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- United Mine Workers of America, District 23, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- United Distillers of America, Ltd., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- United Construction Workers Affiliated with United Mine Workers, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council of Kansas City, MO, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- United Brick and Clay Workers of America, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- United Biscuit Company of America, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- United Biscuit Company of America, United Biscuit Division, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Union Manufacturing Company, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Union Drawn Steel Company and Republican Steel Corporation, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Union Employers Section of Printing Industry of America, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Thompson Products, Inc., 1942 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- G.W. Thomas Drayage and Rigging Company, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Dant & Russell, Ltd., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- McHale Manufacturing Company, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Tex-O-Kan Flour Mills Company, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Texas, New Mexico, & Oklahoma Coaches, Inc., 1943 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Texas Mining & Smelting Company, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Texas Miller Products, Inc., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Tennessee Valley Broadcasting Company, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Tennessee Tricot Mills, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Tennessee Egg Company, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Tennessee Coal, Iron & Railroad Company, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Wm. Tehel Bottling Company (Box 11, Folder 28)
  No date. NO. 12178
- Taylor Colquitt Company and Mrs. Elma La Boone, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Taylor Manufacturing Company, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- The Tappan Store Company, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Taormina Company, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Tampa Times Company, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Sparks-Withington company, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- J.C. Spach Wagon Works, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Southwestern Greyhound Lines, Inc., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Southwestern Electric Service Company, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Southland Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Southern United Ice Company d/b/a Bluff City Delivery, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Southern Silk Mills, Inc., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Communications Workers of America, Southern Division #49, Southern Federation of Telephone Workers (Box 11, Folder 41)
  No date. No Case number.
- Southern Furniture Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- South Atlantic Steamship Company of Delaware, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Somerville Buick, Inc., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Somerville Cream Company, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- The Solvay Process Company, a Corporation, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Somerset Classics, Inc., and Modern Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Smith Victory Corporation (Box 11, Folder 48)
  No date. No case number.
- Vulcan Furniture Manufacturing Location, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Virginia Ferry Corporation, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Victor Manufacturing and Gasket Company, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Victor Products Corporation, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- United States Steel Company, a Corporation, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Tyrrell County Lumber Company, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- William L. Hutcheson, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Tupelo Garment Company, a Corporation, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Tri-State Casualty Insurance Company, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- The Triplex Helix Screw, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- Trimfit of California, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- Toledo Desk & Fixture Company, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Tovrea Packing Company, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- A.J. Tower Company, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- The Times Mirror Company (Box 11, Folder 64)
  No date. Case NO. 10123
- Times-Picayune Publishing Co., 1940 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- The Timken Roller Bearing Company, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Titan Metal Manufacturing Co. (Box 11, Folder 67)
  Testimonies. No date. NO., 6789
- Swan Fastener Corporation, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- United States Gypsum Company, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- United States Cold Storage Corp., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- James C. Petrillo, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Congress of Industrial Organizations (Box 11, Folder 72)
  No date. NO. 695
- United Mine Workers of America, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- United Mine Workers of America (Appendix), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Van de Kampf's Holland-Dutch Bakers, Inc., 1945 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Valley Mould and Iron Corporation, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Vail Manufacturing Company (Box 11, Folder 78)
  Two cases: NO. 9187 (1946) and 794 (1948)
- United Federal Workers of America vs. Harry B. Mitchell, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 79)
- Underground Machinery Company, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Thompson Products, Inc. and Thompson Aircraft Products Company, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 81)
- The Texas Company (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Five separate cases ranging from 1940 to 1951.
- Texarkana Bus Co., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Vulcan Forging Company, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Volney Felt Mills, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- U.S. Truck Company, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Universal Camera Corporation, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Four separate cases. Dates are from 1949 to 1950.
- Tyne Company, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- M.L. Townsend, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Tower Hosiery Mills, Inc., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- The Todd Company, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Tidewater Express Lines, Inc., 1936 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Swift & Company (Box 12, Folder 12)
  Five cases ranging from 1939 to 1946.
- Weyerhaeuser Timber Company, Clemons Branch, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Wallace Manufacturing Company, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Wilson & Company, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Wilson & Co., 1946 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Wilson & Co., Inc., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Wilson & Company, Incorporated, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Williamson-Dickie Manufacturing Company, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Williams Motor Company (Box 12, Folder 20)
  No date. Case NO. 12190
- William Randolph Hearst, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- William Davies Company, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Wilkening Manufacturing Company, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Ford Brothers, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- South Texas Produce Company, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Whitinsville Spinning Ring Company, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Whiting-Mead Company, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Whiting Corporation, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Whitin Machine Works, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- White Construction and Engineering Company, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Wheatland Electric Cooperative, Inc., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Worcester woolen Mills Corporation, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- J.W. Woodruff, Sr. d/b/a Atlanta Broadcasting Company, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Woman's Wear Company (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Woman's Wear Company, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Winona Knitting Mills, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- L.J. Williams Lumber Company, and Varnville Wood Products Company, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Wilson Athletic Goods Mfg. Co, Inc., 1947 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Yawman & Erbe Manufacturing Company, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Sam Zall Milling Co., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Wyman-Gordon Company, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Worcester Wooler Mills Corporation, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Wyandotte Transportation Company, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Washington Dehydrated Food Company, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Warner Bros. Pictures, Inc., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- The Warren Company, Incorporated, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Paterson Steel & Forge Company, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Walworth Company, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Waialua Agricultural Company, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Functions of the NLRB, Statement of Jurisdiction and Powers of the NLB and RLB (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Whittier Mills Company, Silver Lakes Company, Scottsdale Mills, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- F.W. Woolworth, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Winona Textile Mills, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Wine, Liquor and Distillery Workers Union, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Wytheville Knitting Mills, Inc., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Wilson Line, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- L.A. Young Spring & Wire Corporation, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Walt Disney Productions, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- The Wallace Corporation, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  Two cases: 5135/5136 and 66/67
- Wallace Manufacturing Company, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 60)